{
    "questions":[
        {
            "#": "0",
            "question":"blank",
            "options":[""],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "#": "1",
            "question":"What is the best intramural sport?",
            "options":["Flag Football","Flag Football","Flag Football","Flag Football"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "#": "2",
            "question":"Would you marry kim phipps?",
            "options":["Yes!","No","I'd take her to the spring fling","I'm her husband"],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "#": "3",
            "question":"<when does lottie close?>",
            "options":["Way too early","</ when does lottie close>","2:30pm","7px"],
            "answer": 1
        },       
        {
            "#": "4",
            "question":"arrayVal = [“Baby”,”World”, “2 ”, “Peace”, “I I”];\nprint( arrayVal[2] + arrayVal[4] );",
            "options":["Not this one","World Peace","Twin Towers","Staged?"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "#": "5",
            "question":"",
            "options" :"",
            "answer":""
        },        
        {
            "#": "6",
            "question":"Private void doesNothing() { //fill in this line }",
            "options":["","return null","return this","Me.Close()"],
            "answer": 0
        },       
        {
            "#": "7",
            "question":"Why did Suberi end class early",
            "options":["Fire drill","To play ping pong","To grade papers","Computer hungry"],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "#": "8",
            "question":"2 + 2 = ?",
            "options":["22","-4","for","DNE", "4"],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "#": "9",
            "question":"A rectangular garden has a perimeter of 28 meters.\n The length is 5 meters longer than the width, what is the sum of the widths?",
            "options":["10","8","7","6"],
            "answer":20
        },
        {
            "#": "10",
            "question":"jimmyMove",
            "options":["hullothere!!","-4","for","DNE", "4"],
            "answer":""
        },
        {
            "#": "11",
            "question":"Are you smart?",
            "options":["Very, Very Smart!","I sure am stupid","Im as smart as you","waffles?!?"],
            "answer":1
        },
        {
            "question":"this is for the win page! nothing needed here",
            "options":"",
            "answer":""
        },
        {
            "#": "12",
            "question":"You Miss 100% of the Shots You Don’t Take",
            "options":["Wayne Gretzky", "Wayne Gretski", "Whine Grurtsky", "Wanney Gurtis"],
            "answer": 4
        }
    ]
}